[Fangs of Fortune]
[Episode 21]
Situ Ming,
you hid a criminal.
Do you admit your crime?
I wanted to catch Zhao Yuanzhou,
but I found something unexpected.
Zhao Yuanzhou,
no matter where you hide,
it's all in vain.
You underestimate the demon energy tracking spell
of the Chongwu Camp.
Indeed.
You are truly dogs.
Still throwing insults
when you're facing death?
Useless.
Stop, Master!
Jiu!
I won't allow you to hurt my friends.
Bai Jiu,
since you still call me Master,
shouldn't you repay me
and take Zhao Yuanzhou's inner core now?
Repay you?
Why don't we repay you with a beating?
Who helped you when you were the most
confused and helpless?
Who took you in
and taught you medicine?
Will you repay my kindness with hatred?
Jiu,
don't trust him.
He taught you those skills
just to use you to harm people.
That's right.
I must
take responsibility for and fix some mistakes personally.
I won't respect you anymore.
Previously,
I hurt
and lied to my friends.
I will do my best to make up for it.
Sister Pei.
Give me the arrow.
What are you doing?
Jiu.
Don't hurt yourself like this.
Isn't Little Bunny the most timid and afraid of pain?
I am timid
and afraid of pain,
but I'm more afraid of losing you all.
From now on,
I'm no longer a member of Chongwu Camp.
I won't let you manipulate me
as your puppet anymore.
Enough.
Since this is your decision,
don't blame me for being cruel.
Shoot!
They can't be killed.
Demonized humans again?
Zhao Yuanzhou.
Do something.
Stop.
Your magic
is useless against these demonized humans and arrows.
My Demon Slaying Arrow specializes in killing demons.
How can you control it?
Zhao Yuanzhou,
don't waste your energy in resisting.
Surrender.
Oh no.
There's a silver needle on the arrow.
He sealed the Great Demon's touch.
Zhao Yuanzhou.
Now, there's only one last step left
to seal your five senses.
I just need to use the silver needle
to seal your sense of touch
and everything will be set.
Master,
why will sealing a demon's five senses
make them spit out their inner core?
With the five senses sealed,
the physical body will become
a tight jar.
The inner core has a conscious mind
and will struggle
like a drowning person.
Besides,
the Ever-Burning Wood is in Zhao Yuanzhou's body.
After the five senses are sealed,
the fire will burn his entire body.
It'll be torturous.
Zhao Yuanzhou.
The last needle has been completed.
Spit out your inner core.
Zhao Yuanzhou.
Zhao Yuanzhou!
Sir.
What's going on?
Should we just capture him
and take the inner core by force?
Wen Xiao killed the Prime Minister.
Pei Sijing released Zhao Yuanzhou privately.
Arrest them immediately
to wait for their punishment.
Time to eat.
So bland.
I'm a demoness who eats humans.
Fresh human flesh
is much better than fish and meat.
Cut the crap.
The Chongwu Army has seen all kinds of demons.
Look up
at the beast blood talismans.
They're used to suppress you, evil and sneaky demon.
At this time,
you're still in the mood to joke around.
Aren't you worried at all?
It's my first time being a caged animal.
How can I not worry?
I'm talking about Zhao Yuanzhou.
If he goes out of control again,
the world will be over.
Aren't you worried?
I picked up the flagon he left behind.
He drank a lot.
He also has the help Mountain God Ying Zhao's power.
He should be able to suppress the malicious energy temporarily.
Since he chose to run away,
he must still be clear-headed.
He knew he couldn't stay long.
Where would he go?
He'd probably escape to Peach Blossom House.
He set a barrier there.
Outsiders are unable to go in and out.
He once told me
that if one day,
he felt like he was going to lose control,
he would lock himself up.
So even if he went out of control,
he wouldn't hurt anyone.
But this is just a temporary measure.
So,
we should find the Divine Wood as soon as possible
and repair the Baize Token.
Zhuo will find a way.
Yes.
Why are you still struggling?
This is the strongest power in the world.
You can destroy the world
and do anything.
Why do you refuse?
Because I don't want to destroy the world.
No matter what you want,
the invincible power
can do it for you.
I just want the people I cherish
to be safe,
happy,
and content.
How long can you hold on for?
Why don't you just
give yourself to me obediently like before?
Fighting against yourself is like going against the current.
It's futile.
Why endure the pain
of fire burning your heart?
So you don't understand.
What?
♫A lone boat drifts through the world♫
♫The heart feels bitter, then sweet♫
♫Can't distinguish night from day♫
♫At the edge of the dreamscape♫
♫Someone is longing for♫
♫Softly calling for♫
♫A past that can't be brought back♫
♫The world echoes with a single sigh♫
♫Love and hate each fills half the heart♫
♫The years are filled with grudges and grace♫
♫The cry of summer cicadas♫
♫The slumber of winter snow♫
♫No idle wishes and no hopeless longing for eternity♫
♫Who saw the young man in beautiful clothes♫
♫One step at a time, chasing every yesterday♫
♫The sun beams down on the world♫
♫Put everything behind♫
♫You appear in my dream♫
♫The flower in my palm♫
♫Is everchanging♫
♫Sand slips through fingertips♫
♫Struggling again and again♫
♫The sea of suffering has no end♫
♫The spring breeze asks him♫
♫What troubles turned his hair white♫
♫One light, one fire, one crescent moon♫
♫The vow of life and death♫
♫Yet tears leave without a goodbye♫
♫No need to borrow strong wine; it's in my heart♫
♫The dark hair doesn't turn white like snow♫
♫Some other time♫
♫Let's watch the setting sun again♫
♫A lone boat drifts through the world♫
♫The heart feels bitter, then sweet♫
♫Can't distinguish night from day♫
♫The world echoes with a single sigh♫
♫Love and hate each fills half the heart♫
♫Don't forget♫
♫The unforgotten past♫
♫Who saw the young man in beautiful clothes♫
With staggering steps but not asking about tomorrow
If I can live a peaceful
♫The sun beams down on the world♫
♫Put everything behind♫
and carefree life,
♫I see♫
♫You're in front of me♫
No pain
♫Who misses the youth gazing at the bitter sea♫
can bear it
♫He shouted and wanted to be heard by the world♫
It's worth enduring
♫The cruel debts of fate♫
♫Are exchanged for the phrase "I'm willing"♫
♫Wind blows in the distance♫
♫The distant boat approaches the shore♫
This must be where the woodcutter was killed.
The smell of sulfur is so strong.
It's definitely here.
Who is it?
Mr. Zhuo?
Why are you here?
I had to relieve myself.
I understand.
Nonsense.
This smell is not right.
It smells like sulfur.
You are Ao Yin.
Why did you pretend to be the Goddess
and kill the Prime Minister?
And now, you want to pretend to be Mr. Zhuo.
Fortunately, I'm very smart,
quick-sighted,
insightful,
and handsome.
Tell me.
What do you want?
Mountain God Ying Lei,
you're amazing.
No.
Mr. Zhuo would only call me
"Little Mountain God."
Stand there.
Mr. Zhuo.
I was the one who hurt everyone.
Thank you for giving me a chance to follow you.
Are you scared?
Scared?
As long as I can save Wen,
I'm not scared.
Then follow me closely.
Hold it.
I'm afraid you'll get lost.
Who is it?
Ying Lei!
Are you crazy?
Why are you fighting us?
It's not Ying Lei.
It's Ao Yin.
Stop!
Mr. Zhuo!
Brother Zhuo, slow down!
Wait for me.
Hey!
Wait for me!
Watch out, Mr. Zhuo!
She is Ao Yin.
You are Ao Yin.
I have the Cloud Light Sword.
How can I be Ao Yin?
I'm holding my kitchen knife!
I can’t be Ao Yin!
You can get a kitchen knife from any stall,
but the Cloud Light Sword cannot be forged.
That makes sense...
What is the first constellation closest to Mount Kunlun's main door
on the Constellation Formation Map?
I knew it, you're Ao Yin!
Wait.
Wait, wait, wait.
This question is too difficult!
I've never been studious since young.
Hmm.
That makes sense.
What's your dream?
To be a cook!
Who was
the last witness of your beauty in your 200s?
T-T-The mirror in Zhao Yuanzhou's house.
That's right.
He is Ying Lei.
Wait, no.
The first thing you shouted
was for Mr. Zhuo to be careful.
Why didn't you tell me to be careful?
Do I look that despicable?
Yep.
It's confirmed.
He is definitely Ying Lei.
Yes.
Why don't you suspect me?
You're Jiu.
You smell of herbs.
Mr. Zhuo,
you can smell it too?
Since I was young,
I've loved the smell of herbs
because it made me feel
calm
and reassured.
I also like the smell of herbs
and garlic,
onion, green pepper,
vegetables, carrots,
turnips,
and...
Coriander smells good too.
What's wrong with him?
Actually, potatoes are not bad either.
Jiu!
You said
you suspect someone instructed the murderer to commit the crime.
Yes.
They framed me at this time,
probably to stop me
from repairing the Baize Token.
This case is full of errors.
The investigation procedure was a mess.
Do you have any idea
who ordered this?
Wen Zongyu.
But
the Prime Minister was obviously killed by a demon.
Wen Zongyu is a mortal.
How could he make a demon obey him?
You're right.
Previously,
in the illusion of Li Lun,
I saw a female demon
who looked exactly like you.
She seemed to be a subordinate of Li Lun.
Li Lun?
Yes.
But Li Lun is dead.
He burned to ashes
in front of you.
But at that time,
we couldn't find Li Lun's inner core.
Is Li Lun really dead?
Why don't we see his inner core?
The Ever-Burning Wood
is the king of fire.
It can burn everything.
I'm afraid even the inner core
was unable to be preserved.
You mean
Li Lun is not dead?
Pei Sijing, someone wants to see you.
Who?
Why do you ask so much?
Sister Pei.
It's okay.
You be careful.
Ao Yin
can transform at will?
That's difficult to deal with.
If she
finds out our secrets
and habits,
won't it be harder to distinguish her?
Yes.
She's extremely fast.
It's hard to catch her.
The forest is spacious
and humid.
The smell of sulfur
has become too faint to trace.
Based on her lifestyle,
where would she typically hide?
Now is the time
for me, the little Mountain God,
to turn the tide.
When Ao Yin ran away,
I sprinkled
my special spice on her.
The smell is unique.
It's easy to track.
But
Mr. Zhuo said she's extremely fast.
Even if we track her down,
it'll be hard to capture her.
Then just continue to sprinkle spices.
Don't you have another type of spice?
Spice?
Huanling Powder?
Yes.
I have plenty
of Huanling Powder.
But for Ao Yin,
it doesn't seem enough.
What do you need?
That thing?
I got it.
We're missing Kusnezoff Monkshood Root.
Kusnezoff Monkshood Root?
Kusnezoff Monkshood Root
can paralyze people.
It also works on demons.
It can greatly weaken Ao Yin’s speed.
Mr. Zhuo,
aren't I amazing?
You're amazing.
You're indeed the best doctor in Tiandu.
One-Word Spell.
Endure.
Zhen Mei was seriously injured by Zhao Yuanzhou.
It's unknown whether he'll survive.
Once his position becomes vacant,
I hope you, Ms. Pei, can replace him.
Replace him and continue to be your shield?
Why do you think
everyone in the world
is willing to die for you?
Chaos in the Wilderness is imminent.
Demons will swarm here
and take over the mortal world.
Your brother was killed by a demon.
I can relate to this painful experience.
Logically, both of us should
hate demons viciously.
You said you can relate to me
and hate demons to the bone.
Could it be
that an important person to you
was also killed by a demon?
You don't need to ask.
I heard about your rumors before.
You joined Chongwu Camp ten years ago
and were just an ordinary soldier.
But in a short decade,
you rose through the ranks
and became the advisor.
Everyone was puzzled.
That's due to my abilities.
I contributed too much.
I just kept a low profile
and didn't want to show off to the others.
That's because you've done too many dirty things
and you can't see the light.
Zhen Mei is just your puppet.
Zhen Mei
is an orphan.
I adopted him.
Of course he's obedient to me.
But you are so heartless.
In order to save you,
Zhen Mei was heavily injured
and it's uncertain if he'll survive.
And now,
you are using his official position
to negotiate with me.
It seems that
you don't agree.
If you agree,
you can live
and be the commander of Chongwu Camp.
If you refuse,
you have to die
and become food for demons.
It's your choice.
Are you okay?
I’m fine.
Is it the advisor?
Yes.
He is scheming
and vicious.
I'm worried that...
You have no confidence in me?
It's not that I don't have confidence in you.
I just can't make up my mind.
The food will be delivered soon.
I wondered if I should wait for you
to eat it or not?
What?
You need someone for company
to eat a bun and a bowl of rice soup?
Just going with the flow
and finding joy in the pain.
With a best friend's company,
even bland soup is a feast.
Being alone,
even golden goblets
are superficial.
So pretentious.
Did you learn it from Zhao Yuanzhou?
Thank you, Sister.
You even changed your clothes.
What do you know?
The smell of spices
ends here.
She must be inside.
How old are you?
Shameless!
Ying Lei,
are you sure?
Do you know what this place is?
It looks fun.
It's a place you kids shouldn't come.
Goodness.
I'm 237 years and 3 months old.
Mr. Zhuo,
may I ask what age you are this year?
Twenty-four.
Nominal age.
The smell of rouge here is heavy.
In order to cover up her scent,
Ao Yin might choose to hide here.
Then why didn’t she choose
the garbage pile of the underground sewer?
It could've been a better cover.
Right.
Ao Yin is a girl after all.
My grandpa said…
All right.
If you want to continue chatting,
stay here.
If you want to investigate,
shut up and come in with me.
Mr. Zhuo.
I have one more thing to remind you.
Ao Yin
is not only fast and agile.
Her voice
can also be hypnotic.
Remember.
Don't be brainwashed
by her sweet words.
Hey!
Don't you listen to Mr. Zhuo the most?
He said
this is not a place for kids.
What if Ao Yin is really in there?
It might be dangerous there.
Wait here.
Okay.
You're this obedient?
[Tianxiang Pavilion]
Sir, come and play.
Isn't this the dream man of thousands of girls of Tiandu?
It's really Mr. Zhuo Yichen.
What brings him here?
I...
Am I drunk?
Zhuo Yichen.
Girls, come here.
Zhuo Yichen came to Tianxiang Pavilion!
Don't... Don't shout.
I'm not here for fun.
I'm looking for someone.
I understand.
Keep a low profile.
Girls, our chance to get rich is right before our eyes!
Come here.
Come here!
Mr. Zhuo is looking for someone.
You're good at everything.
You're as handsome as the legends say,
with your fair skin and red lips.
Mr. Zhuo.
Brother!
Jiu.
Thank goodness you're here.
No biggie.
Why are you here?
If it weren't for me,
I'm telling you…
you...
What's wrong?
It smells like my spices.
Is that the dancer?
I'm not sure.
The smell is gone.
Keep looking.
It's her.
Let's split up.
Surround her.
Okay.
Let's go.
Miss.
Miss, please wait.
Miss!
Miss.
I'm sorry.
She's getting away!
Brat,
what did you sprinkle on me?
Why am I running so slow?
Stop!
Don't move!
Come back!
Oh my.
Sister Pei.
Why is it you?
How dare you ask me?
We ended up like this because you were
a spy from Chongwu Camp.
I'm sorry.
Sister Pei,
I was wrong.
Sister Pei, you're injured.
Liar!
Traitor!
You...
You are not Pei Sijing!
You are Ao Yin!
You...
Stop!
How dare a minor demon
get in my way?
I'll leave immediately.
I'm going back to the Wilderness.
I'll take him away too.
Wen Xiao?
Zhuo,
it's me.
No.
Zhuo,
look at me.
Look at me.
Shameless!
Zhuo.
Why are you pointing a sword at me?
Zhuo,
I'm Wen Xiao.
Wen Xiao.
Don't you love me?
Zhuo?
Zhuo!
Zhuo.